(Raj:)Wool pants in the desert.
(Raj:)I feel like I've got poached testicles.
(Leonard:)Oh, you poor thing, you're sweating.
(Leonard:)That's so much worse
than having your car stolen.
(Raj:)Insurance is gonna buy you a new car.
It's not gonna de-funk my junk.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, a little less bellyaching.
(Sheldon:)We're Starfleet officers
and a member of the Borg Collective.
(Leonard:)Please, Sheldon, I am so not in the mood.
(Sheldon:)Leonard...
(Sheldon:)...all our lives
we have dreamed of finding ourselves...
(Sheldon:)...inside one of the fantasy worlds
we love.
(Sheldon:)And look at us.
(Sheldon:)At this moment, we are, in fact,
a Star Trek landing party...
(Sheldon:)...stranded in an alien
and unforgiving environment.
(Sheldon:)Relying only on our wits,
our fortitude and our moxie.
(Sheldon:)As long as we have those things...
- ...nothing can stop us...
- Nerds!